idolbin.com 2012-10-19

# Privacy Policy

This policy is valid from 26 April 2012.

This privacy statement describes how  **www.idolbin.com** collects and uses your personal information. Web services and applications that resides on other subdomains of this site has separate privacy policy of their own. This policy is applicable for visiting and interacting with the main site (www.idolbin.com) along with the articles, blog posts and contents inside www.idolbin.com. We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. So it is recommended that you visit this page periodically to get updated with the latest privacy policy of this site. This privacy policy is subject to change without prior notice.

This website and the contents are developed, written and edited primarily by Md. Mahafuzur Rahman (Masum). For questions about this site, please contact  through the [contact me](http://www.idolbin.com/contact-me/) page.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Your information is used for purposes that you expect it to be used for such as answering your questions or providing services you requested.

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to analyze the site traffic and user behavior to eventually improve the contents and usability of this site.

Besides this, the email address that you use when you comment on a post or contacting us via our Contact Form will not be used for any reason but for the purposes of responding to your inquiry and notifications. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
